ultra-case.com 2015-05-26

# Privacy | Ultra-case.com – UltraCase

References in this Privacy Policy Statement to "we", "us" and "Ultra-case" are to JRC Limited (Trading as Ultra-Case). At Ultra-case, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We strive to keep your personal information confidential. Therefore, we have created this privacy policy to make sure you know what information we collect and how we use it. By using our website, you expressly consent to the collection, use ,disclosure and processing of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.In particular, if you are located in a jurisdiction outside the United States, you consent to the transfer of your Personal Information to our servers and computer systems anywhere in the world, including to countries that may not provide an equivalent level of data protection to the laws in your home jurisdiction. If you provide any Personal Information that relates to another person you hereby state and agree that you have obtained proper consent from such person for the use, disclosure, and processing of such Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We will updates this Privacy Policy occasionally when being changes in our practices and services. When we make changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by updating this statement on our Website.

### What information do we collect?

  * register for a Ultra Case account

  * placing orders / gift certificates purchase, we acquire your name, address, delivery address, contact name, contact phone and email.

  * enquiring us by email or by our online contact form requiring assistance.

  * sign up for newsletters, email alerts, and special offers;

  * sign up for, or redeem, special offres;

  * respond to surverys;

  * use our Email-to-a-Freiend or Refer-A-Freind features;

Such information may include your name, telephone number, email address, billing address, shipping address and age. You may also provide us with information about other people, such as their email addresses, if you email a product to a friend or refer a friend to the Site or our promotions.

**The customers financial data and details will not be stored by us.

### What the data will be used for?

We use the personally identifiable information you provide to:

  * fulfill your requests for our products and services;

  * notify you about important functionality changes of the Site;

  * pay earnings; (HOLD)

  * communicate with you about the status of your orders and other inquiries about our products and services;

  * send you information about our products and services;

  * for our internal business purposes, such as data analysis, audits and so forth;

  * help us create content that is most relevant to you; and

  * assessing your request for goods or services, we may use your information for the purposes of the prevention and detection of fraud.

We use your email address to communicate with you about your account and to send you certain notification emails.

When you purchase products from the Ultra-case Website, we may use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send marketing messages about products, services, details of promotions and special offers from Ultra-case Website and also notifications from time-to-time whether or not you created an account with us.

If you do not wish to be contacted for these purposes, we offer a range of ways in which you can inform us about your marketing preferences:

  * Unsubscribe the email notifications on the General page in My Account.

  * All email messages and email newsletters will contain information on how you can unsubscribe; or

  * Send an email to our customer services division on cs@ultra-case.com writing "unsubscribe" in the subject heading; or

  * Call our customer services division - see the "Contact Us" section; or

  * Write to us at: Customer Services, JRC Limited, 2301 Million Fortune Industrial Bldg, 34-36 Chai Wan Kok Road, Tsuen Wan NT, Hong Kong

If you email a product to a friend or refer a friend to the Site or our promotions, we will use your friend's email to send them the e-mail you requested. Your friend's e-mail addresses will only be used for this purpose unless permission is otherwise granted.

We use non-personally identifiable information to monitor the use and performance of the Site to provide assitance to our internal analysis, ie Google Analytics. We can learn more about how people use the Site and their Behavior which helps us improve our products and services and significantly enhance your experience on our website.

### What information do we share with others?

Ultra-case does not share, sell, rent, or trade PII with third parties for their promotional purposes.

We may contract with other companies to provide certain services, including credit card processing, shipping, name and address verification, email distribution, market research and promotions management. We provide these companies with only the information they need to perform their services and work closely with them to ensure that your privacy is respected and protected. These companies are prohibited by contract from using this information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with anyone other than Ultra-case. However, we will not pass your information on to any other third parties for marketing purposes unless you have agreed for us to do so.

One of the purposes for which we may disclose your address and zip code details is to check against the IMRG Security Alert or any other Fraud Prevention Scheme. We may also disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, or when required by law to do so. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.

### The Use of cookies

Like many Internet sites, the site may use small text files called "cookies" that is a small data file that is stored by your Web browser on your computer. We use Cookies to keep track of your current shopping session, to enable you to proceed to checkout at any time and to personalize your online experience.

Cookies do not contain any credit or debit card information. If you do not accept Cookies you will be unable to use this website. Refer to the Help content of your browser for more information on selecting or deselecting Cookies. However, if you disable cookies, you might not be able to access important functions or features of the site and your use of the site may be limited.

### How do we secure your information?

When you place orders or access your account information, we use commercially reasonable and generally-accepted technological safeguards to secure any information we collect about you. The secure server software (SSL) we use encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. In addition, your Ultra-Case account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. You should always take steps to protect the confidentiality of the password you select. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.

You may also choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our website because such information may be required in order for you to register as a member; purchase products or services; participate in a promotion, survey, ask a question; or initiate other transactions on our website.

We work very hard to protect your privacy, but we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. While we use industry-standard precautions to safeguard your personal information, we cannot guarantee complete security.

### Links to Third-Party Sites

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may from time to time include third party links on our Website. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We encourage you to review those policies when you visit those sites. This Privacy Policy Statement only covers our Website and does not cover any other website. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.

### Privacy of Children on Our Website

We respect children's privacy. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information to us, and rely on a parent or guardian to assist you. Children under the age of 13 are allowed to upload graphics and images and to order products with their parent's consent. To order products, the child must indicate his or her age, submit his or her name and his or her mailing address and shipping address if different from the mailing address together with a valid credit card number. In addition, in order to generate custom postage, we must collect and record the following information: the date and time of the custom postage order, a unique order i.d., the amount of postage ordered in the transaction, and the zip code of the recipient of the custom postage. This is the only information collected from a child.

### Sale of assets

In the unlikely event that Ultra-case or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
